<preguntas>
  <pregunta texto="Which of the following employment sectors do you think is more prosperous in our country?">
      <respuesta texto="Construction">
 After so much time making buildings without pause, today our entire national territory has been occupied by apartment complexes; and since there is no forest left to burn and then build, a law has been signed to allow construction in national waters.
       </respuesta>
      <respuesta texto="Tourism">
 After our government declares the increase in employment each year during the months of July and August, it has been decided to modify our calendar to make these two months the only ones existing, so tourists never leave our country; In addition, the entire economy has been modified to make all the work as a waiter or distributor of flyers
      </respuesta>
  </pregunta>
  
  <pregunta texto="What do you think about our society?">
      <respuesta texto="I think we live in a patriarchal society and we have to continue like this.">      
 They have begun to carry out attacks between countries, after a meeting of the world leadership in which alcohol is combined, the ego for "manhood" and the phrase "you do not have balls to ...".
      </respuesta>
      <respuesta texto="I think we have to become a more egalitarian society, it's the most reasonable thing.">
 After the recent attempts to turn our nation into an egalitarian society, with the use of time machines and gases with pathological agents, all our political leaders have agreed for the first time in history, in which they are very comfortable, and they have implemented a strong repression against any group that takes the opposite, under a new law called "Muzzle law".
      </respuesta>
  </pregunta>
  
  <pregunta texto="Do you think we should maintain our monarchy?">
      <respuesta texto="Of course I love our crown.">
 After the great acceptance, based on the divine right of our crown; a group of scientists decided to create an android identical to our beloved queen, to keep her perennial image, this android will consume gin at all hours and continue hunting elephants on their vacations.
      </respuesta>
      <respuesta texto="I think a republic would be better.">
 After a referendum held during the holidays of the royal family, because if it was not impossible to get them out of the palace. The first republic of our country has been formed by having more than 100 parties, with their place in the congress. On the other hand, the royal family will be supported by the retirement of our ex-monarch.
      </respuesta>   
  </pregunta>
  
  <pregunta texto="Do you think that the future of human communication is in social networks?">
      <respuesta texto="Yes, I think they are the future.">
 Because people only used electronic means to communicate, the entire population has begun to live locked in their floors and to establish relationships with people thanks to holograms.
      </respuesta>
      <respuesta texto="No, I think they are stupid">
 Social networks are declared illegal, making thousands of young people not able to communicate with each other without using emojis. OMG !!
      </respuesta>
  </pregunta>

  <pregunta texto="How do you prefer to buy your games?">
      <respuesta texto="I always buy them in physical format.">
 After the disappearance of all online video game stores, and the industry was not ready to return to the world of disc games and expansions, video games disappear as entertainment, making table games become the number one entertainment of the masses, creating a competitive spectrum that moves millions of young and old old people.
      </respuesta>
      <respuesta texto="I only buy in digital.">
 After the increase in sales of games in online platforms, permanent discounts have been implemented in all online stores, causing thousands of studios to collapse due to the few benefits they generate by making survival battlle royales with heroes games.
      </respuesta>
  </pregunta>

  <pregunta texto="What do you think about having a firearm to defend your family?">
      <respuesta texto="I don't like that people can have a gun.">
 After years of peace after illegalizing and destroying any firearm, we have just received hostile contact with aliens and we are only going to be able to defend ourselves with sticks and stones. From this newspaper we greet our new masters. #GloryToTheWarxianEmpire
      </respuesta>
      <respuesta texto="I think it's a right that we all have.">
 After the massification of the firearms after signing the treaty with which every newborn was forced to have a Beretta 9mm, we have reached the point where our economy has put aside our local currency to replace it with ammunition of 5,56 caliber. 
      </respuesta>
  </pregunta>

  <pregunta texto="Do you like that our hymn has no lyrics?">
      <respuesta texto="I do not care in the least">
 Attention!! attention!!, our neighboring country declares war threatening to bomb us, after a misunderstanding during the football world to sing the typical "lo Lolo lololo" that accompanies our hymn, which in their native language means "We're going to skin you motherf@$ร@$รง ".
      </respuesta>
      <respuesta texto="I think it's a very important problem.">
 While the people fervently debated which of the two anthem proposals was better, if the most lively version to Latin-trap rhythm or a classic military march, our government has taken advantage to lower the average salaries to less than half without anyone give an account.
      </respuesta>
  </pregunta>
</preguntas>